Today we're going to talk about the interview process.
The other thing that you need to think about when you're into the interview process is your cell phone.
Today, so many of us have got cell phones and they're part of our hip.
They're in our pockets; they're in our purses.
They're everywhere in our life.
We use them all the time.
They're ringing, they're buzzing, they're going off at all times.
Kiss of death in an interview is that if you don’t care enough to turn your phone, I probably don't care enough to hire you.
My thinking is and has always been and the people that I have discussed this with have always said the same thing.
If you're going in for an interview, make that interviewer the most important person at that time.
The best way to do that is to leave your cell phone in your car that's in the parking lot, because there is nothing as important as that interview when you're there.
Nothing.
You can always get voicemail.
That's why they have them.
Turn your phone off, leave it in your car.
When you go in, be focused and ready to go for the interview.